- Yes!
是的！
Winter break has officially begun!
寒假正式开始了！
Goodbye, backpack.
再见，书包。
Hello, couch back.
你好，沙发靠背。
- This is the last time you'll see me in pants
这是你最后一次看到我穿裤子
'til New Year's.
直到新年。
- And of course, what would the holidays be
当然，没有大胆的Dicky舔冰冻邮箱的节日
without daring Dicky to lick the frozen mailbox?
会是什么样子？
- [muffled] So uncool, guys.
[含糊不清]伙计们，这太不酷了。
- Okay, fun time's over.
好了，玩乐时间结束了。
Let's talk gift-snooping strategy.
我们来讨论一下偷看礼物的策略。
So...
那么...
Where do you think Mom and Dad hid the presents this year?
你觉得今年妈妈和爸爸把礼物藏在哪里了？
- [muffled] Attic.
阁楼。
- What?
什么？
- [muffled] Attic!
阁楼！
- Wait a minute.
等一下。
What about the attic?
阁楼怎么了？
- Ricky, you're a genius.
里基，你真是个天才。
- [muffled] That's what I said!
我就是这么说的！
- I hope Mom and Dad got us a Maxbox.
我希望妈妈和爸爸给我们买了Maxbox。
- I know; last year's gaming system is so two years ago.
我知道；去年的游戏系统已经是两年前的了。
All: Ooh.
哦。
- Jackpot.
中大奖了。
All right, Nicky...
好吧，尼基……
Work your magic.
施展你的魔法吧。
- Socks.
袜子。
Picture frame.
相框。
[sniffs]
（嗅）
Personalized mugs.
定制的杯子。
- What?
什么？
- What are we, teachers?
我们是什么，老师吗？
- Guys, my snooping senses are tingling.
伙计们，我的侦查直觉在发痒。
All: Yeah?
是吗？
- There's no Maxbox here.
这里没有Maxbox。
- If there's no Maxbox,
如果没有Maxbox，
what's the point of having Christmas at all?
那圣诞节还有什么意义呢？
[bells jingling]
（铃铛响）
- No, no, no.
不，不，不。
I see four children who just made the naughty list.
我看到四个孩子刚上了淘气名单。
All: Santa?
全体: 圣诞老人?
- We're sorry.
- 我们很抱歉。
We just really wanted a Maxbox.
我们只是真的很想要一个Maxbox。
All: Dad?
全体: 爸爸?
- Yeah, just trying on the old suit.
- 是的，只是试穿一下旧衣服。
Can't let the kids at the store down.
不能让商店里的孩子们失望。
They look forward to it every year.
他们每年都期待着。
Everybody loves Santa.
每个人都喜欢圣诞老人。
He's jolly and fun!
他既快乐又有趣！
[all agreeing]
[全体同意]
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho!
哈哈哈哈哈！
By the way, you're all in a lot of trouble.
顺便说一句，你们都有大麻烦了。
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
[有节奏的拍手] - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
- [whistling melody]
- [口哨旋律]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na-na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[bells jingling]
[铃铛叮当响]
- I can't believe you kids were snooping for presents.
- 真不敢相信你们这些孩子竟然在偷看礼物。
- I can't believe this is the first year you've caught us.
- 真不敢相信这是你第一次抓到我们。
- You're ruining the magic of Christmas
- 你们正在破坏圣诞节的魔力
and breaking Santa's heart.
和伤了圣诞老人的心。
- Honestly, I don't even know how to punish you for this.
- 老实说，我甚至不知道该怎么惩罚你们。
- You should probably take away some of our presents.
- 你们可能应该拿走我们的一些礼物。
- Like the personalized mugs.
比如那些定制的杯子。
- That'll teach us.
那会教训我们的。
- Okay, look, we're really sorry we snooped,
好吧，听着，我们真的很抱歉偷看了，
but isn't not getting a Maxbox punishment enough?
但难道没有得到Maxbox的惩罚还不够吗？
- Don't worry.
别担心。
The real Santa will bring us one.
真正的圣诞老人会给我们带一个来。
- With your gimme-gimme-gimme attitude,
以你这种‘给我给我’的态度，
that would be a Christmas miracle.
那才是一个圣诞奇迹。
- You know what else would be a Christmas miracle?
你知道还有什么会是圣诞奇迹吗？
- If you sounded a little less jolly
如果你在惩罚孩子时听起来不那么愉快。
while you punish the children.
而你却在惩罚孩子们。
- Okay, well, your Mom's gonna take all the fun
- 好吧，你妈妈会让我在这里失去所有乐趣。
out of this for me.
但你们必须学会理解金钱的价值。
But you guys have to learn the value of a dollar.
你妈妈和我辛苦工作才买得起那些礼物，
Your mother and I work hard to get those gifts,
而你们只关心你们没有得到的东西。
and all you care about is what you're not getting.
- 你爸爸说得对。
- Your father's right.
我认为这是完美的惩罚。
And I think that is the perfect punishment.
你们四个将在寒假期间在店里工作。
The four of you are gonna spend your winter break
什么？
working at the store.
- 太好了，现在我还得穿裤子。
All: What?
所有人：什么？
- Great, now I have to wear pants.
太好了，现在我得穿裤子了。
- Sorry, kids,
抱歉，孩子们，
but you just joined the ranks of the working class.
但你们刚刚加入了工人阶级的行列。
Merry Christmas!
圣诞快乐！
[all groan]
（所有人抱怨）
- Okay, bright side.
好吧，积极的一面。
Mom and Dad are gonna pay us,
爸爸妈妈会付我们工资，
so maybe we can make enough money as a group
所以也许我们作为一个团队能赚到足够的钱
to buy our own Maxbox.
去买我们自己的Maxbox。
- Whew.
- 呼。
All: Nicky!
所有人: 尼基！
- What? I'm not on the clock yet.
- 怎么了？我还没开始上班呢。
- Dude, you look ridiculous in that outfit.
- 伙计，你穿那套衣服看起来很滑稽。
- Dude, you're wearing the same thing.
- 伙计，你穿的也是一样的。
- Yeah, but you look ridiculous in it.
- 是啊，但你穿起来看起来很滑稽。
- Oh, looking good, Santa's little Harpers.
- 哦，看起来不错，圣诞老人的小哈珀们。
- See how cute they are?
- 看他们多可爱？
Ooh, I just love Christmas so much!
哦，我太爱圣诞节了！
I'm so excited I get to spend the holidays with you guys.
我太兴奋了，能和你们一起过假期。
I used to come here when I was your age...
我以前在你这个年纪时也常来这里...
♪ And now I get to work here ♪
♪ 现在我在这里工作 ♪
- I love your Christmas spirit, Josie.
乔西，我喜欢你的圣诞精神。
You kids could learn something from her.
你们这些孩子可以从她身上学到些东西。
- They already have.
他们已经学到了。
Show your Mom what you're gonna say to the customers.
给你们妈妈展示一下你们要怎么对顾客说。
Both: Drop your kids with us to play!
一起: 把孩子交给我们来玩吧！
Both: While you shop for the holiday!
一起: 你就可以安心购物过节了！
- Ooh, I need an elfie.
哦，我需要一张精灵照。
[camera clicks]
[相机咔嚓声]
- Ho-ho-ho-ho.
- 呵呵呵呵。
Well, merry Christmas, little Timothy.
嗯，圣诞快乐，小蒂莫西。
And don't forget your Christmas cookies.
别忘了你的圣诞饼干。
["Joy To The World" playing]
[《普世欢腾》播放]
♪ ♪
- Make way for Mrs. Claus
- 给克劳斯夫人让路
coming through with reindeer cookies.
带着驯鹿饼干过来。
I just checked on our little elves, Tom.
我刚去看了我们的小精灵，汤姆。
This is so good for them.
这对他们太好了。
They're learning what hard work is all about.
他们在学习什么是辛勤工作。
- Well, they don't have to look far
嗯，他们不必远寻
to find a great role model.
就能找到一个伟大的榜样。
- Oh, thanks, honey.
哦，谢谢，亲爱的。
I am working really hard cranking out these cookies.
我真的很努力在做这些饼干。
- I was talking about me.
我指的是我自己。
I'm the hardest-working man
我是雪业中最勤奋的人。
in "snow" business.
请，你知道做这么多饼干有多难吗？
- Please, do you know how hard it is
而且孩子们喜欢驯鹿饼干。
to crank out all these cookies?
你知道他们更爱什么吗？
And children love reindeer cookies.
[孩子们欢呼]
[kids cheering]
孩子们欢呼
- Do you know what they love more
你知道他们更喜欢什么吗
than cookies shaped like reindeer?
比做成驯鹿形状的饼干更受欢迎的？
Real-life reindeer.
是真正的驯鹿。
Come here, Rudolph.
过来，鲁道夫。
Come here, little guy.
过来，小家伙。
Come on.
来吧。
Ho-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho. - Aww.
哈哈哈哈哈。
- They should call you "shameless" Claus.
他们应该叫你“无耻”克劳斯。
- No-ho-ho-ho-ho-ho.
不哈哈哈哈。
- And every kid gets a yellow vest
每个孩子都会得到一件黄色背心，
so we don't lose anybody.
这样我们就不会有人走失。
Our number one priority is keeping them safe.
我们首要的任务是确保他们的安全。
- Then you might want to keep them away from Dicky.
那你可能想让他们远离迪基。
- Don't pick your nose.
别挖鼻孔。
Have some class.
有点风度。
Let Dicky teach you how to do a snot rocket.
让迪基教你如何擤鼻涕。
- Ho, ha, no!
哦，哈，不！
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
好了，好了，好了。
Let's put you up front at check-in and pick-up.
我们让你在登记和接人时站在前面。
[sighs]
[叹气]
All right, you guys are good to go.
好了，你们可以走了。
I'm gonna go spread Christmas cheer.
我要去传播圣诞快乐。
- Um, with that old thing?
- 呃，用那个老东西？
- It'll get me through the holidays.
- 它能让我度过假期。
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
♪ 我们祝你圣诞快乐 ♪
[strings twang]
[弦乐拨动]
♪ I'm gonna go get more tape ♪
♪ 我要去拿更多胶带 ♪
- Okay.
好的。
So...you elves ready to get working?
那么...你们这些小精灵准备好开始工作了吗？
- Yeah, we're gonna have our Maxbox in no time.
是的，我们很快就会有我们的Maxbox了。
- And all we have to do is play with kids.
而且我们只需要和孩子们玩耍。
I love children.
我喜欢孩子。
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
[all shouting in pain]
（所有人痛苦地喊叫）
- Longest...day...
最长...的一天...
...of my life.
...我生命中的。
- Work...is such hard work.
工作...真是辛苦的工作。
- I hate children.
- 我讨厌孩子。
- We are very proud of how hard you worked today.
- 我们为你今天如此努力工作感到非常骄傲。
- Now, for the best part...
- 现在，最精彩的部分来了...
- Quads be gettin' paid!
- 四头肌们要领薪水了！
- Cash money!
- 现金到手！
- Hello, Maxbox.
- 你好，Maxbox。
- $10 each?
- 每人10美元？
Okay, that's it?
- 就这些吗？
- Good-bye, Maxbox.
- 再见，Maxbox。
- Now you're starting to understand the value of...
- 现在你开始明白...的价值了。
Cash money!
现金！
- [chuckles]
（轻笑）
- Can you believe this?
你能相信吗？
- Yeah, it's terrible.
是啊，太糟糕了。
- Um, Dicky...
呃，迪基……
Whatcha got there?
你那儿有什么？
- Parents gave me money when they picked up their kids.
家长们接孩子时给了我钱。
- Oh, that's great. We got tips!
哦，太好了。我们有小费了！
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
哇，哇，哇，哇。
We didn't get tips.
我们没有得到小费。
Dicky got tips.
Dicky收到了小费。
- For our work!
- 因为我们的工作！
- And we agreed to pool our money to buy a Maxbox together.
- 而且我们同意把钱凑在一起，一起买一个Maxbox。
- That's almost enough money to buy your own Maxbox.
- 那几乎足够买你自己的Maxbox了。
- Ooh.
- 哦。
I was gonna buy some sweet foot rides.
我本来打算买一些甜美的足部骑行装备。
That's what Dicky calls shoes now.
这就是Dicky现在对鞋子的称呼。
But...
但是...
I do like the sound of my own Maxbox.
我确实喜欢拥有自己的Maxbox这个想法。
All: What?
所有人：什么？
- You can't buy your own Maxbox.
你不能买你自己的Maxbox。
- Why not?
为什么不行？
President George Jefferson says I can.
乔治·杰斐逊总统说我可以。
- Grr!
呃！
- I want to pa-rum-pa-pum-pummel him!
我想揍他一顿！
- Okay, easy there, little drummer boy.
好了，别激动，小鼓手。
- That's our money too!
那也是我们的钱！
- Don't worry, guys.
别担心，伙计们。
Look, tomorrow, all we have to do
听着，明天我们只需要
is trick Dicky out of his greeter job,
让Dicky失去他的迎宾工作，
and then we get all the tips.
然后我们就能拿到所有的小费。
- Whew.
呼。
Both: Nicky!
尼基！
- What, you've never seen an angry elf
怎么，你以前没见过生气的精灵穿内裤吗？
in his underwear before?
哦，是的。
Ooh, yeah.
所有人：圣诞老人，回来！
All: Santa, come back!
等等，孩子们。
- Ho-ho-hold on, there, kids.
圣诞老人吃饼干时牛奶喝多了，
Santa had a little too much milk with his cookies,
现在他需要去去去！
and now he needs to go-go-go!
我其实不需要去。
I don't really need to go.
Santa just needs a little "me" time.
圣诞老人只是需要一点“我”的时间。
- I could use some "me" time.
- 我也需要一些“我”的时间。
I haven't had a break in hours.
我已经好几个小时没休息了。
- [chuckling]
- [轻笑]
- What's so funny?
- 有什么好笑的？
- Nothing, it's just, you know...
- 没什么，只是，你知道的...
A break, from making cookies.
从做饼干中休息一下。
You're just following a recipe, right?
你只是在按照食谱做，对吧？
- Just following a recipe?
- 只是按照食谱做？
Ha!
哈！
Being Santa is a vacation
当圣诞老人比准时做出成千上万块饼干轻松多了。
compared to getting thousands of cookies out on time.
哦，我觉得当圣诞老人比烘焙难一点。
- Oh, I think being Santa's a little harder than baking.
每个孩子都是一个新的挑战。
Every kid is a new challenge.
我得让每个孩子都充满圣诞精神。
I've got to fill each of them with the Christmas spirit.
这可没有食谱，安妮。
There's no recipe for that, Anne.
你说着“呵呵呵”，
- You say, "ho-ho-ho,"
然后坐享其成我的饼干，
and take credit for my cookies
坐在那肥大的圣诞老人屁股上。
while sitting on that big, fat Santa butt.
好吧，别提我的欢乐制造者了。
- Okay, let's leave my merry-maker out of this.
好吧，让我们别提我的欢乐制造者了。
But in the spirit of the season,
但在这个季节的精神中，
I'm gonna give you a little gift.
我要给你一个小礼物。
I'll bake your little cookies,
我会烤你的小饼干，
and you can try being Santa.
你可以试试当圣诞老人。
Here.
这里。
- Deal.
成交。
Now, hand over the beard.
现在，把胡子交出来。
And you can keep the Santa-tude.
你可以保留圣诞老人的态度。
- Ooh, Mrs. Claus has claws.
哦，克劳斯夫人有爪子。
Rawr.
吼。
- Dolla-dolla bills, y'all.
各位，都是美元啊。
- Okay, time for operation...
好了，行动时间到了...
Tricky Dicky.
狡猾的迪基。
Hey, can I talk to you for a sec?
嘿，我能和你谈一会儿吗？
- Don't bother.
别费心了。
You're not gonna trick me into leaving my post.
你不会骗我离开岗位的。
- Oh, you're right.
哦，你说得对。
You know, you're too smart for that.
你知道吗，你太聪明了，不会上当的。
[gasps]
[倒吸一口气]
Ooh, look, a really cute girl over there.
哦，看，那边有个非常可爱的女孩。
- Ooh, Dicky likey!
哦，迪基喜欢！
- It's almost too easy.
这简直太容易了。
I'll take first shift.
我先值班。
- Uh, no.
呃，不行。
I'll take first shift.
我先值班。
- [laughs]
（笑）
No.
不行。
I'm the one who tricked him.
是我骗了他。
I'll take first shift.
我先值班。
- There's a simple way to settle this.
有一个简单的方法来解决这个问题。
Whoever calls dibs. Dibs!
谁先喊‘我要了’。我要了！
- Really? I was the one who got him.
真的吗？是我把他弄来的。
[all shouting]
（大家都在喊）
- ♪ Dashing through the snow ♪
♪ 在雪地上飞驰 ♪
♪ In a one-horse open sleigh ♪
♪ 坐在一匹马拉的雪橇上 ♪
♪ O'er the fields we go ♪
♪ 我们穿越田野 ♪
♪ Now I cannot play, ha-ha-ha ♪
♪ 现在我不能玩了，哈哈哈 ♪
Just...
只是...
[laughs]
（笑）
- Stop.
停。
Stop!
停！
It's not like any of us are gonna pull a Dicky--
我们中没人会像Dicky那样——
pocket the money and buy our own Maxbox.
把钱藏起来然后买自己的Maxbox。
- Yeah, we trust each other, right?
是啊，我们互相信任，对吧？
- After all, it is Christmas.
毕竟，今天是圣诞节。
-All: Every quad for themselves!
各凭本事！
[all clamoring]
（众人争抢）
- Call me.
给我打电话。
She already memorized my number.
她已经记住我的号码了。
Okay, you guys can clear out.
好的，你们可以离开了。
I'm back.
我回来了。
- You leave it, you lose it.
你放弃了，就失去了。
- No.
不。
- Okay, I got here first!
好吧，我先到的！
[all shouting]
（所有人喊叫）
[shouting continues]
（喊叫继续）
- Guys, stop!
伙计们，停下！
Fighting's getting us nowhere.
打架对我们没有任何好处。
Okay, there are four kids left.
好吧，还剩下四个孩子。
How about we each take one and keep the tip?
我们每人带一个孩子，然后分小费怎么样？
- Um...there are only three kids left.
- 呃...只剩下三个孩子了。
- Well, where'd that Frankie kid go?
- 那Frankie那孩子去哪儿了？
- That little meatball must have rolled away!
- 那小肉丸子肯定是滚走了！
- This is not good.
- 这可不妙。
If anybody finds out we lost a kid, we'll get fired,
如果有人发现我们弄丢了一个孩子，我们都会被炒鱿鱼，
and none of us will get a Maxbox.
那样我们谁也拿不到Maxbox。
- Okay, emergency quaddle.
- 好吧，紧急会议。
Okay, Dicky, Ricky, you find Frankie.
好，Dicky，Ricky，你们去找Frankie。
Nicky and I will stay here and watch the kids, all right?
Nicky和我留在这里看着孩子们，好吗？
Break!
休息！
Oh, hey, kids.
哦，嘿，孩子们。
So what do you guys like to do for fun?
你们喜欢做什么来玩呢？
- Watch the elf boy dance.
- 看小精灵男孩跳舞。
- Ow!
- 哎哟！
- Okay.
- 好的。
Keep on dancing!
继续跳舞！
- Okay.
- 好的。
Who's next?
下一个是谁？
[gasps]
[喘气]
Well, hello, cute little girl.
嗯，你好，可爱的小女孩。
What would you like for Christmas this year?
今年圣诞节你想要什么礼物？
- A slingshot!
- 弹弓！
- Oh, a--
- 哦，一个--
can you think of a safer toy?
你能想一个更安全的玩具吗？
- You sound like my Mom.
- 你听起来像我妈妈。
- Oh, really?
- 哦，真的吗？
Well...
嗯...
No cookies for you.
没有饼干给你。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
["Joy to the world" playing]
[screaming]
- Okay, step one...
[chuckles]
Pre-heat oven to 350.
Ooh, it sounds exhausting.
[chuckles]
Well, if you can't stand the heat...
[screams]
Get me out of the kitchen!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
哈哈哈哈！
Gah!
啊！
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧。
Minor setback.
小挫折。
There.
好了。
I can still read...
我还能读...
Some of it.
一部分。
Okay, uh...
好吧，呃...
Is that "baking soda" or "bake with soda"?
那是“小苏打”还是“用苏打烤”？
Probably soda. Everybody loves soda.
可能是苏打。大家都喜欢苏打。
- [grunting]
（咕哝声）
- Oh, no.
哦，不。
Frankie's Mom is headed this way.
弗兰基的妈妈正朝这边走来。
Oh, here.
哦，这里。
Hey, Mrs. Cupertino.
嘿，库珀蒂诺太太。
How's the shopping going?
购物进行得怎么样？
- Good, I've just come to check on my little Frankie.
很好，我只是来看看我的小弗兰基。
- Oh, he's great!
哦，他很好！
Oh, look at him over there,
哦，看他在那儿，
playing like little kids do.
像小孩子一样玩耍。
- Easy there, cowboy Billy .
- 悠着点，牛仔比利。
- So just keep shopping.
- 继续购物吧。
Frankie's fine.
弗兰基没事。
Oh, look, camping stuff!
哦，看，露营用品！
- No, no, I just don't think you realize
- 不，不，我只是觉得你没意识到
what a huge responsibility a real pony is.
一匹真正的马是多么巨大的责任。
Okay, okay, you know what will make you feel better?
好吧，好吧，你知道什么会让你感觉好点吗？
Some cookies.
一些饼干。
Ugh.
呃。
[muttering]
[咕哝]
[pounding]
[敲打声]
Aw, come on!
哦，拜托！
♪ All ye faithful ♪
♪ 所有忠诚的人们 ♪
♪ Joyful and triumphant ♪
♪ 快乐而胜利 ♪
[pounding]
[敲打声]
- There he is.
- 他在那儿。
- Boys, stop right there!
- 孩子们，停在那儿！
- Dad?
- 爸爸？
- No, no, it's Mom.
- 不，不，是妈妈。
And I am losing it up here.
我在这里快要崩溃了。
It's a really tough crowd,
这真是一群难伺候的观众，
and I need more cookies.
我需要更多的饼干。
- No problem.
- 没问题。
We're headed in the kitchen anyway.
反正我们正要去厨房。
- No, there's no time!
- 不，没时间了！
I have an emergency stash in the storeroom.
我在储藏室里有一批紧急储备。
Okay, it's just that way.
好的，就在那边。
- But--
- 但是——
- Just go!
- 快去！
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪哦，圣诞树♪
♪ 哦，圣诞树 ♪
♪ How lovely are your... ♪
♪ 你的美丽多么... ♪
- Oh, no, he's headed for the kitchen.
哦，不，他正朝厨房去。
Hold down the fort!
守住阵地！
- I'm tied to the fort!
我被绑在阵地上！
- Okay.
好的。
No, no.
不，不。
No!
不！
[muttering]
[咕哝]
[groans]
[呻吟]
[呻吟声]
- Dawn. - Huh!
- 黎明。 - 啊！
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
- 你在干什么？ - 没什么。
- Good, I need your help.
- 好，我需要你的帮助。
But don't tell your mother.
但别告诉你妈妈。
Can you make anything out on this card?
你能看懂这张卡片上的内容吗？
- Uh...
- 呃...
It says here you have to...
上面写着你必须...
Sing.
唱歌。
Sing Christmas Carols...
唱圣诞颂歌...
To the cookies while baking them.
在烘烤饼干的时候。
- Really?
- 真的吗？
- Yep, alone.
- 是的，独自一人。
- I'm not singing to the cookies.
- 我不会对着饼干唱歌。
♪ Hark how the bells, sweet silver bells ♪
♪ 听那钟声，甜美的银铃声 ♪
♪ All seem to say throw cares away ♪
♪ 一切似乎都在说，抛开烦恼 ♪
♪ Christmas is here, bringing the cheer ♪
♪ 圣诞节来了，带来欢乐 ♪
♪ To young and old, meek and the bold ♪
♪ 无论老少，无论温顺还是勇敢 ♪
- ♪ Ding dong ding dong, that is their song ♪
- ♪ 叮咚叮咚，那是它们的歌 ♪
♪ With joyful ring, all caroling ♪
♪ 带着欢乐的铃声，到处唱颂歌 ♪
♪ One seems to hear words of good cheer ♪
似乎能听见四处传来欢欣的话语
♪ From everywhere, filling the air ♪
从每个角落，充盈在空气中
♪ Oh, how they pound, raising the sound ♪
听那有力的回响，提升着音量
♪ O'er hill and dale, telling their tale ♪
越过山丘与溪谷，传递着它们的故事
♪ Gaily they ring, while people sing ♪
它们欢快地鸣响，伴随着人们的歌唱
♪ Songs of good cheer, Christmas is here ♪
歌声中满是喜悦，圣诞已至
♪ Merry merry merry merry Christmas ♪
欢乐欢乐欢乐欢乐的圣诞节
- So, Toby, what do you want for Christmas?
那么，托比，你圣诞节想要什么？
- To give Santa a present.
给圣诞老人送个礼物。
- Oh!
哦！
Oh, that is so sweet.
哦，真是太贴心了。
And what do you have for Santa?
那你给圣诞老人准备了什么？
- [grunts]
哼！
Don't look at me, Santa!
别看我，圣诞老人！
- Oh.
哦。
Oh!
哦！
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不！
No! Ahh!
不！啊！
- Bad news, Mom.
坏消息，妈妈。
Some animal must have gotten into your emergency cookies.
一定是有动物偷吃了你的应急饼干。
It's empty.
空了。
- Maybe we have rats.
也许我们家有老鼠。
- Or a sneaky little reindeer.
或者是一只狡猾的小驯鹿。
- Why aren't you guys looking for Frankie?
你们怎么不找弗兰基呢？
- We were looking for cookies.
我们刚才在找饼干。
- At a time like this?
这种时候？
Okay, his mother's going to be looking for him.
好吧，他妈妈会来找他的。
- Here comes Josie.
乔西来了。
Play it cool.
保持冷静。
- Hey, guys, where's Frankie?
嘿，伙计们，弗兰基在哪儿？
Nicky said you took him to see Santa.
尼基说你带他去看圣诞老人了。
- Santa?
圣诞老人？
- Doesn't ring a jingle bell.
这可不像是圣诞节的铃声。
- Oh, no, you guys didn't lose him, did you?
哦，不，你们没把他弄丢了吧？
- I wouldn't say, "lose."
我不会说‘弄丢’。
I'd say, "lost," 'cause it's already happened.
我会说‘已经丢了’，因为事情已经发生了。
- Oh-oh-oh-oh!
哦-哦-哦-哦！
And here comes Frankie's Mom.
弗兰基的妈妈来了。
She trusted us with her child.
她把她的孩子托付给了我们。
And I trusted you.
而我信任了你。
- We need a Christmas miracle.
- 我们需要一个圣诞奇迹。
- ♪ Merry merry merry merry Christmas ♪
- ♪ 圣诞快乐，圣诞快乐 ♪
♪ Merry merry merry merry Christmas ♪
♪ 圣诞快乐，圣诞快乐 ♪
♪ Ding-dong ♪
♪ 叮咚 ♪
[bell dings]
[铃声叮咚]
Oh, they're ready.
哦，他们准备好了。
Well, they smell good.
嗯，他们闻起来很香。
[laughs]
[笑]
Oh, holy night.
哦，神圣的夜晚。
They're delicious.
它们真美味。
- There you are.
你在这里。
- And there you are.
- Frankie's Mom in the village.
Frankie的妈妈在村里。
- Woot-woot! - Where's my Frankie?
喔喔！ - 我的Frankie在哪里？
- Here's a present, Santa! - Oh!
这是给圣诞老人的礼物！ - 哦！
- Merry Christmas!
圣诞快乐！
- Oh, this is quite the stocking stuffer.
哦，这真是个不错的袜子填充物。
- So where is he?
- 他在哪儿？
- Dicky!
- 迪基！
- Is that a...
- 那是个...？
- Just get rid of it.
- 赶紧处理掉。
- Yule log, coming in hot.
- 圣诞柴火，热腾腾的。
[dramatic Christmas music]
[戏剧性的圣诞音乐]
♪ ♪
["Joy to the world" playing]
["普世欢腾"播放中]
- The truth is, your little Christmas miracle
- 事实是，你的小圣诞奇迹
is right here.
就在这里。
- I think this calls for a little holiday miracle music.
我想这需要一点节日奇迹音乐。
Be right back.
马上回来。
- Well, he looks like he had a blast.
嗯，他看起来玩得很开心。
Here you go, kids.
给你们，孩子们。
Thank you, and merry Christmas.
谢谢，圣诞快乐。
- Whoa.
哇。
- You know, if we combine our tips,
你知道吗，如果我们把小费合起来，
we can afford one Maxbox right now.
我们现在就能买一个Maxbox。
Agreed?
同意吗？
Both: Agreed.
同意。
- Agreed.
- [groans]
（呻吟）
[chuckles]
（轻笑）
Look how happy they are.
看他们多开心。
Santa was a big hit this year.
今年圣诞老人很受欢迎。
- Hmm, and so were your cookies.
嗯，你的饼干也很受欢迎。
- [laughs]
（笑）
- This is what Christmas is all about, Tom.
这就是圣诞节的真谛，汤姆。
- Yeah, I guess we kind of lost track of that.
是啊，我想我们有点忽略了这一点。
- Hmm.
嗯。
Yeah.
是啊。
Can we switch back now?
我们现在可以换回来了吗？
I hate being Santa so much!
我太讨厌扮成圣诞老人了！
- I never want to bake another cookie again.
- 我再也不想烤饼干了。
- Who's ready for some holiday cheer?
- 谁准备好迎接节日气氛了？
♪ Deck the halls with boughs of holly ♪
♪ 用冬青枝装饰大厅 ♪
♪ Fa-la-la-la-- ♪
♪ 啦-啦-啦-啦- ♪
Oh, what's the point?
哦，有什么意义呢？
- ♪ ♪
- Guys, thank you so much,
- 伙计们，非常感谢你们，
but you didn't have to do this.
但你们不必这么做的。
- We were gonna spend our money on a Maxbox,
我们本来打算买个Maxbox，
but we figured it was better spent
但觉得这钱花在
on someone who's trying to spread Christmas cheer.
努力传播圣诞快乐的人身上更好。
- Hey, our kids learned a lesson.
嘿，我们的孩子也学到了一课。
It's a Christmas miracle!
这真是个圣诞奇迹！
- Show us what you got, little strummer girl.
给我们看看你的本事，小吉他手。
- All right, here we go.
好吧，开始了。
- Go, Josie.
加油，乔西。
♪ We... ♪
我们...
All: ♪ Wish you a merry Christmas ♪
大家：♪ 祝你♪ 圣诞快乐 ♪
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
♪ 我们祝你♪ 圣诞快乐 ♪
♪ And a happy new year ♪
♪ 和一个快乐的新年 ♪
♪ Good tidings we bring ♪
♪ 我们带来好消息 ♪
♪ To you and your kin ♪
♪ 给你和你的家人 ♪
♪ We wish you a merry Christmas ♪
♪ 我们祝你♪ 圣诞快乐 ♪
♪ And a happy new year ♪
♪ 和一个快乐的新年 ♪
[dog barking]
[狗吠]
- Hey, it's snowing!
嘿，下雪了！
[bells jingling]
♪ Hark how the bells, sweet silver bells ♪
♪ All seem to say throw cares away ♪
♪ Christmas is here, bringing the cheer ♪
♪ To young and old, meek and the bold ♪
♪ Ding dong ding dong, that is their song ♪
♪ With joyful ring, all caroling ♪
♪ One seems to hear words of good cheer ♪
♪ From everywhere, filling the air ♪
♪ Oh, how they pound, raising the sound ♪
♪ O'er hill and dale, telling their tale ♪
♪ 越过山丘和谷地，讲述着他们的故事 ♪
♪ Gaily they ring, while people sing ♪
♪ 欢快地响起，当人们歌唱 ♪
♪ Songs of good cheer, Christmas is here ♪
♪ 欢乐的歌曲，圣诞节已到来 ♪
♪♪
- ♪
♪